<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writings on Makonnen</title>
    <link>http://makonnen.sh/writings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writings on Makonnen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://makonnen.sh/writings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Binary Bomb Lab</title>
      <link>http://makonnen.sh/writings/binarybomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://makonnen.sh/writings/binarybomb/</guid>
      <description>I don’t usually get all hyped up about educational exercises, but the Binary Bomb Assignment is a standout. It’s not your typical assignment; it’s like a puzzle where you get this compiled binary file—aka the “bomb”—and you’ve got to disassemble and debug it to make it go away. The bomb comes in phases, each with its own challenge related to assembly language, like stack operations or register manipulations. It’s hands-on and actually makes learning about how high-level code turns into machine instructions pretty engaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Existing on the internet (I)</title>
      <link>http://makonnen.sh/writings/existing_on_internet_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://makonnen.sh/writings/existing_on_internet_1/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t posted on Instagram in about five years, and Lord knows when I last touched Facebook. At this point, there’s really no reason for anyone over 18 to have Snapchat installed - so that can be ignored. I still throw out the occasional tweet, but it’s mostly just a place for random notes now. Lately, I’ve been using BeReal a bit more - seems like a fun spot to hang out for now, but I even see it dying down as a fad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflections from this year</title>
      <link>http://makonnen.sh/writings/2023reflections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://makonnen.sh/writings/2023reflections/</guid>
      <description>The Highlights Reel This year&amp;rsquo;s been quite the ride, kicking off with a new bundle of joy in the family (sorry Sari, your nickname suggestion didn&amp;rsquo;t make the cut), followed by a lively baptism celebration. My sisters and old Alexandria buddies made their way to NYC, and the uni crew stuck to our annual hangout tradition. Oh, and I finally set foot in Europe for an ACM Security conference in Copenhagen - cold but fun!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highway guardian</title>
      <link>http://makonnen.sh/writings/sheperd_of_the_highways/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://makonnen.sh/writings/sheperd_of_the_highways/</guid>
      <description>I’ve got one uncle who seems to be the unofficial guardian of the highways. Out of the blue, he’ll call you up just to let you know that traffic is jammed at some random intersection you haven’t seen in months. He just can’t help but keep everyone updated. More often than not they surprisingly end up being useful and ahead of news reports themselves. Every time we get these updates they&amp;rsquo;re kind of funny and oddly comforting at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sardine in outer space</title>
      <link>http://makonnen.sh/writings/sardine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://makonnen.sh/writings/sardine/</guid>
      <description>I always bring up this comic book to my sister since she can’t for the life of her, remember reading it. Although we read it all the time since it was one of the few colored comic books our library had more than a decade ago.&#xA;I honestly just remember a few things:&#xA;Goofy and whimsical main character, outwits all her enemies Strange pirate crew. They were all weird. But fun.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
